Hello, today in this video we will tell you
about the III Lord Max Protect plan. Max Protect is a new plan from the
III Lord company, which
offers unlimited coverage
at an affordable premium. This plan has some features
such as unlimited coverage, higher sub-share
options, worldwide coverage without any
copayment. The video is going to be detailed in
which we will tell you what
is covered and what is not covered in this plan. Apart from this, we
will also share with you the benefits, features, eligibility criteria, sum in short, and the premium of this plan. But
before starting the video, one important thing is that
if you have not yet subscribed to our channel, then
subscribe so that
you get the right information at the right time.
I would like to introduce myself.
My name is Kajal. I keep giving you
updates related to health and life insurance
through this channel and
also give you advice on every insurance-related problem. Our team has
12 years of experience in the insurance industry
and we also provide claims-related consultancy.
Let's get started today.
Before starting the video, we will
see the claim settlement ratio and income ratio of ICICI Lombard. The claim settlement
ratio is 88.5% and the income ratio is 91.6%.
Data on Age 2021 & 22. First of all,
in this plan you get worldwide
coverage without any copayment. This means
that if you want to take global coverage outside India as well,
then it is available in this plan.
You
get two variants in this plan - Classic and
Premium.
Worldwide coverage is available to you in the premium variant. Now the second is
in this plan, you get a guaranteed cumulated
bonus of 20% to 100%. This means
that the bonus you get in this plan
is guaranteed and if you get any claim in the future, then
it will not be reduced.
You are given a bonus of 20% to 100%.
Now thirdly, in this plan, higher
subsumed options are available to you. This means that now
you can take up to 10 crores in this plan.  You
can also take a sum insured of Rs. 10 lakh. In this you get the
option of unlimited sum insured. The
insurance company will pay whatever claim you make
if you choose the unlimited sum insured
option in this plan. Just to
remind you, if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, then
subscribe and like.
If you have any questions related to this plan, then
ask us in the comments. Now let's
talk about some common benefits of both the variants.
First of all, let's talk about the coverage of this plan.
In this plan, the
cost of your inpatient treatment
is covered. It means if you are
hospitalized for 24 hours, then during that time all
your room IC expenses,
nursing expenses, surgeon, anesthesia, medical practitioner, consultant, specialist, physician,
medicine, diagnostic expenses will be
covered.
Talking about the short sum insured options,
in this plan you can avail sum insured up to Rs. 50 lakh, 1 crore, 3
crore, 5 crore, 10 crore and unlimited.  You
can choose the option for sum assured. By
choosing the unlimited option, you can
claim as much as you want. There is no limit. Let's
talk about the entry age. The
minimum entry age is 18 to 65 years for adults. For
dependent children, it is 91 days to
25 years under the family floater policy. The
minimum age in individual policy is 6 years.
Now let's talk about room rent eligibility.
You can take any room in this plan
except suite category.
You will be paid the actual amount. The
next benefit is guaranteed cumulated bonus.
In this plan, you will be given a no-claim bonus on 20 days,
maximum up to 100% and this
bonus will not be reduced even if a claim is made.
Just to remind you once again, if
you have not yet subscribed to our channel, then
subscribe and
like the video if you like it.
If you have any questions related to this plan, then
ask us in the comments.
Apart from this, emergency room ambulance is covered.
Hospitalization
refill benefit up to Rs. 10,000 is available to you in this plan
Day care treatment is covered for unlimited times
after the sum Some domicile
treatments and AYUSH hospitalization are also
available to you here Up to the sum shot
Modern treatments are covered in which the company
covers advanced procedures like
robotic surgery, brain stabilization,
stem cell therapy, oral chemotherapy and many
more modern treatments are also covered Up to
ten sum shot maximum limit is Rs. 1 crore
Pre-hospitalization is covered in this plan for up
to 60 days and post-
hospitalization is covered up to 180 days
E-consultation is available to you for unlimited
times Bariatric surgery is
covered for up to 10 times The short policy term will be of 1,
2 and 3 years If you are
taking a policy for 2 years, then you will get a discount of 10% on the premium. You will get a discount of 10% on the premium
only after paying the second year premium If you
take a policy for 3 years, then you will get a discount of
10% on the premium after paying the second year premium  You will
get a discount and on paying the premium for the third year,
you will get a discount of 15% here.
Now let's talk about the differences in these variants.
Home care treatment up to ₹1
lakh is available here only
in the premium variant.
Worldwide cover up to ten sum shot maximum up to 3
crore will be given to you only in the premium variant.
Claim protector is available in this plan
only in the premium variant, in
which your non-payable
items are included in this plan.
Prevent health checkup up to ₹1000000 will be
available to you only in the premium variant.
Emergency air ambulance up to the sum
shot is available to you only in the premium variant.
Option to change the room
category is available in this plan
only if you choose the classic variant. If you
want to change the room category from any
room category to single private room, you
can do so here, which reduces your premium.
OPD and deducted are
not available in this plan.  And there are no riders
available in this plan. Just as a
last reminder, if you have
n't subscribed to our channel yet, please
subscribe and
like the video if you like it. If you have any questions related to this plan,
ask us in the comments. There is a payment to the zonal.
In this plan, if you get treatment from a lower zone to a higher zone,
you will receive a
payment. Now let's know about the waiting period. The
initial waiting period
is 30 days. For specific diseases, you have a
waiting period of 24 months.
For bariatric surgery, the waiting period
is 3 years. And for pre-assisting diseases,
you have a waiting period of 48 months,
which you can also reduce by
paying an additional premium in the policy for 24 months. After opting for the optional rider,
you can see the premium and zone details of this plan
on your screen.
[Music]
So friends, that's all for today's video. We
hope you found the information given in this video
really useful. We keep bringing important information
related to health and life insurance for you.  All the
people who are connected with us, please continue
with us in this journey and if you
are new to our channel then please
subscribe to our channel and our